<u>RESUME</u>

Gadge Yogesh Gajanan BSc (Computer Science) Cell No: 8329035905/9604839631 E-mail: <u>yogeshgadge92@gmail.com</u>

ADDRESS

R.No:16-Sanskruti Apt. Near Kewal Park, Chunchale Shivar, Ambad .Nashik – 422010.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Solution-driven professional excelling in highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to challenges and focused on customer satisfaction. Proven experience developing consumer-focused web sites using HTML, CSS, JQuery,Ajax, PHP and JavaScript. Responding to challenges by designing and developing solutions and building web applications aligned to customer's services. Self-motivated PHP Developer with high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in role with company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Total Year of Work Experience: Around 4 Years

- > PHP DEVELOPER(CI-framework) Solace infotech Pvt Ltd NASHIK (JUNE 2017 TO PRESENT)
- Collected, defined and translated user requirements into project designs and implementation plans.
- Used programming capabilities in PHP, SQL and JavaScript and other libraries as needed.
- Optimized and repaired corporate website based on PHP, Mysql technology
- ▶ PHP DEVELOPER(CI-framework) Dotphi infosolution Pvt Ltd NASHIK (Sept- 2015 to JUNE 2017)
- Analyzed requirements and designed, developed and implemented software applications.
- Communicated often with business clients throughout the process and gave updates of work.
- Presented training to staff as needed.
- > PHP DEVELOPER(core php) Shloka Innovative Solutions (January- 2015 to May-2015).
- **▶** Data Entry Operator Datamatics Global Services Ltd (1-year).

EXTRA CARICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Received **first** prize in C-programming language contest.
- Certificate for Successful participation in N. S. S. at graduation level in 2012-2013.

COMPUTER SKILLS

- ➤ Client site Language
 - JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax
- ➤ Web Technologies.
 - PHP, HTML/HTML5, JavaScript/Jquery, Bootstrap, CSS. .
- Couputer Languages known.
 - PHP, java, C, C++, HTML/HTML5.
- > Frameowrk (php)
 - Codeigniter, Wordpress(basic), OpenCart(basic)
- > PHP web services
 - REST & generic web services.
- Database Handled.
 - Mysql, Access.
- ➤ MS-CIT (Microsoft Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- > Editor
- Notepad++, Adobe Dream-weaver, Ultraedit.
- > Tools
- Postman.

Projects

❖ ArtToframe (https://www.arttoframe.com/)

· Technology: PHP, Mysql, Ajax, JQuery

· Role : PHP Developer

· Link: https://www.arttoframe.com/

Description: ArtToframe is e-commerce product which is specially know for its personalization of framing,mats ,glass etc. Arttoframes has 52 kind of different customize product type which daily active user more than 3000-5000. I have work in a team of 20 developers who were responsible for providing live development service for customizing of daily framing on 52 different product. We also worked on the backend admin panel to maintain the daily order system. I also contribute on implementing and custom developing of 2 different products compatible for mobile and desktop versions which is scripted by using HTML5.

BIFROST (http://list.graspy.com/)

· Technology : PHP(Codeigniter), Mysql, Ajax , JQuery

· Role: PHP Developer

· Link : http://list.graspy.com/

Description: Bifrost is a tool for leads generation and used by authenticated partner to validate the information using different filters(APIs) by providing the require information to form.

Main Focus: Bifrost is a tool for leads generation and used by authenticated partner to validate the information using different filters(APIs) by providing the require information to form.

❖ EDUCATION CHOICES (https://www.educationchoices.com/)

· Technology : PHP(Codeigniter), Mysql, Ajax , JQuery

· Role : PHP Developer

· Link : https://www.educationchoices.com/

Description: <u>educationchoices.com</u> is the education opportunities providing platform where student will find online, campus option in the top schools. I worked on different APIs, migrate recordings onto multiple server, admin site different reports.

Main Focus: To provide educational opportunities to student and career professionals for their education without placing their family responsibilities on hold.

IDEALERP (http://www.idealerp.in/)

· Technology : PHP(Codeigniter), Mysql, Ajax , JQuery

· Role : PHP Developer

· Link : http://www.idealerp.in/

Description: An online web application for managing all the industrial work at a centralized point which includes modules like Purchase, Quality control, Store, Production, Sales, Marketing, Maintainance, Payroll, HRMS and Accounts. Application handles tasks like creation of BOM, make purchase order ,sales order and production entries ,defined product line and then workorder processing, managing machine breakdown logs and repair entries, defining sales target and allocated that targets to employees. Generates reports on the quarterly or yearly basis for forecasting. Accounting transactions like receipt and voucher ,credit/debit note entries,managing outstanding of vendors/dealers.Application also handles the management, approval and verification of stock at the store.

Responsibilities:

- Designed and automated standard functionalities as well as build custom features in modules like accounts payable, accounts receivable, general ledger, production, inventory management, subcontracting to meet various gaps identified during requirements gathering.
- Managed client relationship to ensure programs are developed within the clients specific parameters/requirements.
- Design and implementations of functionality of all modules defined above.
- User Registration and role management.
- Database creation and management in Mysql.
- Dynamic menu integration.
- Email and SMS API Integration.
- Project and team management activities.

Air Force School,Ojhar(http://www.afschoolojhar.com/)

Technology: PHP(Codeigniter),,Mysql,Ajax,JQuery

• Role : PHP Developer

Description: Dynamic website for Air Force School, Ojhar developed in PHP and Mysql which is providing the ability for admin to manage page interface like add/update new images, page content, headres etc.

Responsibilities:

- Server side code development.
- Email Integration.
- Database creation and management in Mysql.

❖ KaalSarp Puja In Nasik

• Technology: PHP, Mysql, Ajax, JQuery

• Role : PHP Developer

Description: Dynamic website for KaalSarp Puja developed in PHP and Mysql which loads in two languages English and Marathi.

Responsibilities:

- Server side code development.
- Email Integration.
- Database creation and management in Mysql.

❖ Gram Surksha Yantrana

Technology: PHP(Codeigniter),,Mysql,Ajax,JQuery

Role: PHP DeveloperLink: http://gramsu.com/

Description : Dynamic website for Gram Surksha Yantrana developed in PHP and Mysql.

Responsibilities:

- Server side code development.
- Retailers Online Balance(using payment gateway instamojo).
- Sms Integration.
- Email Integration.
- Database creation and management in Mysql.

ACADEMIC CREDENTIALS

No.	Qualification	Year of Passing	University/ Board	Class obtained
1.	S.S.C.	March 2008	Amaravati	1 st Class
2.	H.S.C.	Feb.2010	Amaravati	Higher 2 nd Class
3.	BSc in Computer Science	2015	Pune	Appeared

Personal Details

Name : Yogesh Gajanan Gadge Fathers Name : Gajanan Shriram Gadge

Date of Birth : 26 Aug 1992
Marital Status : Married.
Nationality : Indian.
Sex : Male.

Language Known : English, Hindi, Marathi.

Hobbies : Playing, Drawing, Learning New Things.